I am passionate about problem solving and innovation through software development. I enjoy researching, developing, and designing web applications for various platforms, as well as solving technical problems.

My goal is to land a job in software development and apply my knowledge and skills towards a company's objectives.

Work History

2022-02 - 2022-8

Computer Programmer

Batanes General Hospital

- Analyzed and designed a relational database in SQL for a VB.NET "Leave Management System" project.
- Used Microsoft Visual Studio and VB.NET packages to test, modify code, and work to implement a system into a system.
- Provided
- Participated in a project's requirements analysis and worked with internal teams to create software design.

2020-06 – 2022-01

I.T. Assistant

Batanes Electric Cooperative, Inc

- Participate in continuous improvement by generating suggestions, engaging in problem solving activities to support teamwork.
- Created plans and communicated deadlines to complete projects on time.
- Used Microsoft Word and other software tools to create documents and other communications.
- Offered friendly and efficient service to customers, handled challenging situations with ease.
- Collaborated with team members to achieve target results.

Education

2022-8 – Present

MERN full-stack Web Development bootcamp student

Uplift Code Camp and Department of Information Communication Technology

- Learn to build a front-end web app with React.js, the Redux toolkit, and npm packages in a short time frame.
- Build responsive website using HTML and CSS only.
- Creates Web-based game using Vanilla JavaScript.
- Uses Gitlab as a project repository.

2015-06 – 2019-07

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology University of Cagayan Valley



Alden Derf Fabro
Full-stack Web Development
Student

Contact

- 09193633590
- aldenderfc.fabro99@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/alden-derf
- https://github.com/Adenderf
- Mahatao, Batanes

Technical Profile

- React JS
- Responsive Design
- Document Object Model
- Redux
- APIs
- Node JS
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Adobe Photoshop
- Gitlab
- MongoDB
- Express JS

Coding Certificates

• Responsive Web Design View Certificate